wholesalecentral.com 2017-11-17

# Privacy Policy | WholesaleCentral.com

Thank you for visiting our website (the "Site") and reviewing this Privacy Policy. This Site is owned, operated and controlled by Sumner Communications, Inc. This Privacy Policy applies to this Site only. It does not apply to other websites owned by Sumner Communications or to which we may link. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our Site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information, and your ability to control our disclosure of it. Please review this Privacy Policy before submitting any personal information to Sumner through this Site. By your use of our Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. All reference to "Sumner," "we," "our," and "us" in this Privacy Policy refer to Sumner Communications, Inc. For information on use of our Site, please read our Site Terms and Conditions of Service at <http://www.wholesalecentral.com/tos.htm>. 

**Information Which We Collect**  
We collect two types of information from you: (i) information that you knowingly and voluntarily supply to us (e.g., through a registration process, sign-ups, or other interaction with the Site); and (ii) information that is derived through automated tracking mechanisms. 

**Voluntary Information**  
In order to fully access the Site, you may need to complete a registration process and some of this information will identify you personally or enable you to be identified personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us. This Privacy Policy refers to such information as "personally identifiable information." This may include your name or associated company name, postal address, home or work telephone number, password, email address, credit card information and information used to verify your identity or to avoid fraud. This personal information is collected from you in a variety of ways, including your responses to correspondence, registering for a service, or participation in interactive aspects of our Site or related services. In addition, during the registration process, you may knowingly and willingly provide additional personal information, such as, your user name, your website or blog address, photographs, information about your hobbies and interests, your gender, or your birthday. 

**Information Collected Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies**  
Like many websites, our Site may use "cookies" or other similar tracking technologies to collect information which will help us to improve the quality of our services and to make it easier for you to navigate the Site. This information typically includes your IP address, the address of the web page you were visiting when you accessed the Site, the name of your operating system (such as Windows or Macintosh), the name and version of your browser (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox), pages navigated during your visit to the Site, and the date and time of your visit, among other things. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, most computers allow you to change your browser setting to prevent acceptance of cookies. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, certain features or parts of the Site may not work properly. 

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use the information that we collect from you to improve our Site, our services, and your experience with our Site and services. For example, we would use your information for any of the following purposes: 

  * to respond to your queries and requests;
  * to assist you with managing your account and passwords;
  * for security, credit card or fraud prevention purposes;
  * to process applications submitted by you and communicate with you about transactions you have requested;
  * to undertake, with your consent, any other promotional activities such as providing information about special events, blogs, and chats;
  * to communicate with you about our products and services, and other information related to our business that may be of interest to you;
  * for internal marketing analysis, such as identification of trends;
  * to provide you with effective customer service and/or technical support; or
  * to improve the design of our Site.

**Sharing Information**  
We may share your personal information with third parties without your authorization as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This may include, selling mailing and/or email lists that may contain your contact information to third parties, providing suppliers and other third parties who we may retain to analyze data we collect, including personal information, to help us improve our products and our Site. In addition, if you order a product or service from us, we may provide personal information to suppliers and other third parties to create the order, process credit card payments, detect and prevent fraud, enable delivery of such product or service, or send mail or email or provide customer service. These third parties, including suppliers, are not authorized by us to use your personal information in any other way. 

We may supplement the information that you provide to us with other information that we receive from third parties. We do this for marketing purposes in order to provide the most appropriate products and services to meet your needs. 

We may transfer, sell or assign your personally identifiable information to any entity to which we divest all or a portion of our business (for example, in connection with our sale of a brand), to the extent that you provided such information to the specific portion of our business (or brand) that is being divested, or otherwise in connection with a merger, consolidation, change in control, reorganization or liquidation of all or a portion of our business. 

Please note that we will release your personal information if required to do so by law, or by search warrant, subpoena or court order to comply with legal requirements, cooperate with law enforcement, prevent fraud and other crimes, and protect legal rights. There are circumstances in which we may share the personal information in our databases with unrelated third parties. For example, we may disclose the personal information we collect on this Site without notifying you when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or a regulatory requirement; to comply with a subpoena or court order; to cooperate with law enforcement or other governmental investigations (without necessarily requiring the law enforcement or government agency requesting the information to formally serve us with a subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce a contract; to protect the legal rights, property or safety of Sumner, our affiliates, and their employees and agents, other users or the public in general or to protect your vital interests. We also reserve the right to report to appropriate law enforcement or government agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful without providing notice to you. 

In addition, we may share specific personally identifiable information as disclosed in a specific Privacy Notice posted on the page or area of this Site where you provided that information. You will receive notice when your personally identifiable information might be provided to any third party for any reason other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you will have an opportunity to request that we not share such information. 

**Children's Privacy and Parental Controls**  
We do not use our Site to knowingly solicit personally identifiable information from or market to anyone under the age of majority in his or her country. If you have not reached the age of majority in your state or country you may not use this Site and should not provide any information about yourself through this Site. Our goal is to comply with applicable laws and regulations relating to the collection and use of information from children, including the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of the United States and other applicable laws or regulations. Please be aware that there are parental control tools available online that can be used to prevent children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors. If you believe that we received information from a child or other person protected under such laws, please notify us immediately by postal mail addressed to Sumner Communications, Inc., 24 Stony Hill Road, Bethel, CT 06801 or by email at [privacy@sumnercom.com](mailto:privacy@sumnercom.com) and we will take reasonable steps to remove that information from our database. 

**How Long We Retain Your Personal Information**  
We keep personally identifiable information only as long as we need it for the purpose for which it was originally collected (or to which you have subsequently consented) or for other legitimate purposes (such as regulatory compliance), or as permitted by applicable law. 

**External Links**  
For your convenience, we may provide links to websites owned and operated by unrelated third parties. Such third party sites should have their own privacy policies which we recommend you review prior to interacting with such site. This Privacy Policy applies only to the personally identifiable information collected through this Site and you agree that Sumner has no liability with respect to such third party sites or their privacy practices. 

**Policy Changes**  
Sumner may, in its sole discretion and at any time and for any reason, change this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for reviewing the notice and applicable changes. Your continued use of the Site, after changes or modifications are posted, constitutes your acceptance of such changes. If you do not agree with the changes to this Privacy Policy, do not use the Site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. 

**Data Security Commitment**  
We take reasonable precautions to keep your personally identifiable information secure. All personally identifiable information is subject to restricted access to prevent unauthorized access, modification or misuse. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have industry standard measures in place to safeguard and secure information and data we collect through the Site. It is important that you understand, however, that no website or database is completely secure or "hacker proof" and we cannot guarantee security of the information you submit to us. You are responsible for taking personal steps to protect your personally identifiable information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your password from unauthorized use or disclosure. 

**Contacting Us; Opt Out**  
At your request and where the law requires us to do so, we will make good faith efforts to confirm what personally identifiable information we hold about you, update your information, remove your information, and/or correct any inaccuracies in such personally identifiable information if you contact us at <http://www.wholesalecentral.com/aboutus.htm> to submit such requests. You can opt-out of receiving promotional or commercial email from us by following the instructions contained in the emails or by visiting <http://www.wholesalecentral.com/aboutus.htm>. We may decline to process a request that is unreasonable, jeopardizes the rights or privacy of others, is impractical or for which access is not otherwise required. 

**Who to Contact**  
Please contact us at by visiting <http://www.wholesalecentral.com/aboutus.htm> or write to us at Sumner Communications, Inc., 24 Stony Hill Road, Bethel, CT 06801 if you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy or to report any violations of the Privacy Policy. We will endeavor to respond to you within 24 to 48 hours in most cases. 

**Governing Law / Effective Date**  

This Privacy Policy and our Privacy Notices are governed under the laws of Connecticut without regard to its conflict of law provisions. 

You and Sumner agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in Connecticut, and You and Sumner further agree that, in the event that there is any claim, dispute, or other matter in question arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy and our Privacy Notices, the enforcement of any provisions therein, or breach of any provisions thereof, it shall be submitted to and adjudicated by the Federal, state or local courts, as appropriate, in the State of Connecticut. 

California Residents: If you reside in California and have provided personally identifiable information to us, you may request information about our disclosure of certain categories of personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us by visiting <http://www.wholesalecentral.com/aboutus.htm> or writing to us at Sumner Communications, Inc., 24 Stony Hill Road, Bethel, CT 06801. 

This policy was last updated on October 15, 2013.
